领带不错
Nice tie.
你这次是不是应该报警了
Are you at least gonna call the cops this time?
不了  不想让他们
No, then they might stop,
才开始吸引我眼球的时候
just when they're beginning to...
就被迫停止
capture my eyes.
行了  爸爸  让罗德里戈收拾吧
Come on, dad. Let Rodrigo do this.
你的关节炎很明显...
Your arthritis is obviously--
我可以自己收拾草地
I can pick up my own lawn.
其实  如果你想的话
You know, if you wanted,
你大可终止这一切
you could put an end to all this.
我当然知道
Oh, of course.
还有其它方式可以拯救公司
There are other ways to save the company.
我把公司搬去中国
I'm only moving it to China
只是因为我太爱芙蓉炒蛋了
because I'm craving egg foo yung.
我刚和一些投资商
You know, I just got off the phone
通过电话
with some investors.
是嘛  他们想要控股吧
Yes, and they want a controlling interest.
我们得留在这里
We get to stay here with the people
和公司的忠实员工共进退
who've been so loyal to this company.
让每个人都能保住饭碗
Everyone keeps their jobs.
120年来这一直都是家族生意
It's been a family business for 120 years.
我不可能让...
There's no way that I'm letting...
怎么了
What's wrong?
爸爸
Dad?
我需要你载我去看医生
I need you to drive me to a doctor.
他的情况真够糟糕的
This would totally suck.
病人近期经常去中国
Patient's visited China a lot recently.
会不会是日本乙型脑炎病毒
What about the JBE virus?
在你提供下一个愚蠢的想法前
Why don't you check his vaccination record
为什么不先看看他的疫苗注射记录呢
before you make another stupid...
我的亲娘
O.M.F.G.
纸杯蛋糕半价
50% off cupcakes.
病人病得有多严重
How sick is the patient?
这个优惠今天就到期
'cause this expires today.
中心浆液性视网膜病变
Central serous retinopathy?
指向A型人格
It's linked to type "A" personalities.
眼底镜检结果正常
Funduscopic exam was normal.
如果你不让我看邮件
If you don't let me read my email,
我就没法看这封由你前任上司
then I won't be able to read the email to the entire staff
发给全体员工的邮件了
from your ex-boss.
谢谢
Thank you.
"上月  我与一名普林斯顿普雷斯波罗
"Last month, I had an incident
教学医院的员工发生了摩擦
involving another P.P.T.H. employee.
由于我的纪律听证会还未进行
Though I can't speak to the details of the case
我不能详谈事件的细节
while my disciplinary hearing is pending,
但我希望你们知道
I want you to know that I have completed
我已自愿完成性骚扰课程
voluntary sexual harassment training.
谨此
And on a personal note,
若我的行为引起任何人的忧虑
if my actions caused anyone distress,
我真诚致歉"
I sincerely apologize."
你被炒定了
You are so fired.
什么  他道歉了
What? He apologized.
什么  就因为他说他致歉吗
What? Because he said he apologized?
他说的是  他对某人  也就是你
He's saying he's sorry that someone, namely you,
反应过激  也就是打了他  感到抱歉
overreacted-- namely, by punching him.
他摸了我的屁股
He grabbed my behind.
暗语说那是庆祝的一掌
Word is it was a celebratory slap
恭喜你首次完成
after you completed your first-ever
脑动静脉畸形栓塞治疗
AVM embolization.
他摸了我屁股  他为此道歉了
He grabbed it, he apologized for grabbing it,
他也正在为此接受教育
and now he's taking classes because he grabbed it.
上课一举只会惹人同情
The classes make him sympathetic.
反而  使那个冥顽不灵的攻击者
Which, in turn, makes his unrepentant attacker...
成了恶人一个
evil.
所以
Which, in turn,
说白了  就是你被炒
in turn, makes you so fired.
赌一百块我不会被解雇
100 bucks says I won't get fired.
你最好不要和我赌
Oh, you don't wanna bet me.
天呐
Oh, my.
你被解雇了
You're fired.
我  打的赌是...
I--the bet is--
-但我以为  -在...
- But I thought... - After...
然后我...
Then-- I...
只要
If only...
我们是在打赌听证会后我会否被炒
The bet's that I'll get fired after my hearing!
那个我也赌
I'll take that action too,
但你的一百块已经有半张进我口袋啦
but you're already a c-note in the hole.
你迟到了
You're late.
考虑到我不在这里工作
Considering I don't work here,
所以  是我来早了
arguably, I'm early.
珍珠耳环
Pearl earrings?
及膝裙
Knee-length dress.
穿这么体面昨晚在何处逍遥啊
That's not a very shameful walk of shame.
我刚参加了一个面试
I was at a job interview.
希望进行得很不顺利
I hope it went terribly.
塞得·巴顿
Thad Barton?
我们是只救治那些有钱的白人吗
We only help rich white guys?
我是个讲求回报的人
I am an equal opportunity exploiter.
助我者我助也
I only help those who can help myself.
我得给我的部门找赞助人
I have a department to re-fund.
阿托品中毒
Atropine poisoning.
他要把自己的公司搬去中国
He's moving his company to China,
员工便把做成他模样的假人吊了起来
and his employees are hanging him in effigy.
他们可能动了真格
Could have moved on to the real thing.
瞳孔正常
Pupils are normal.
甲状腺毒症
Thyrotoxicosis?
这主意  不算糟
Not...a terrible idea.
我去给他服丙硫氧嘧啶[抗甲状腺药物]
I'm gonna go give him P.T.U.
外加细心呵护
and T.L.C.
我其实不知道后者所言何物
I have no idea what that second one stands for.
东西看起来都很大
Things don't seem small anymore, they--
我睡了个午觉醒来
I woke up from a nap and,
所有的东西就由极小变为了硕大
everything went from really small to really huge.
这样的话  这些巨型药球
Well, then, these giant balls of medicine
就没用了
are not gonna work anymore.
这一改变反而使事情变简单了
The change actually makes things simpler.
你的枕叶出了问题
Your occipital lobe is acting up,
导致你偏头痛
giving you a migraine.
我头不痛
I don't have a headache.
并不是所有的偏头痛都会让人头疼
Not all migraines present that way.
这种病被称为爱丽丝综合症
It's called Alice in Wonderland syndrome.
真的吗
Seriously?
我从来不开玩笑
I never joke.
好消息是
Good news is,
这病是可以通过药物进行治疗的
it's treatable with medication.
坏消息是
Bad news is...
这病可能会让你
it can make you very,
赴重要约会时严重迟到
very late for very important dates.
我有时也会开玩笑啦
I sometimes joke.
谢谢你  医生
Thank you, doctor.
如果你真的想要谢我的话
Well, if you really want to thank me,
我的部门现在不成部门
my department's not really a department.
因为我的老板说他没钱
'cause my boss says he doesn't have the money.
你  就形成了鲜明对比
Which provides a nice contrast...with you.
我们正在想办法从预算中节省资金
We're trying to find money in our budget
这样我们就不用将公司搬到海外了
so we don't have to move our operations overseas.
我懂了  你说你们也"没钱"嘛
I get it. Answer's no.
刚才我多嘴了
Shouldn't have said anything.
很高兴症状出现在
I'm just glad that the symptoms showed up
你去中国前
before you left for China.
我可不认为那里的医生
'cause I'm not sure the doctors over there
会这么乐观
would be so optimistic,
介于...
considering...
你们在说什么
What are you guys talking about?
只是在感叹文化差异有多么巨大
Oh, just how different the two cultures are.
比如  对于精神病的看法
For example, our opinions on mental illness.
在这里  我们认为是正常且可治疗的
Here, it's considered a normal and treatable condition.
一切都好吗
Is everything okay?
一切都好
Everything's fine.
但我能让你转院去
I could have you checked into a facility
专治精神疾病的机构
that exclusively treats mental disorders.
这主意怎么样
How does that sound?
只要能让他病情好转
Whatever's gonna get him better.
先试试药物治疗吧
Let's try the medication first.
我雇你了
You're hired!
你们一定会喜欢奇斯和陶博的
Oh, you guys are gonna love doctors Chase and Taub.
别在小个子医生面前表现你的纳粹情结就好
Keep your nazi sentiments quiet around the little one.
你弄到钱了吗
You got the money?
怎么弄的
How?
病人是个精明的商人
Patient's a smart businessman.
他正一手破坏数千就业机会
He's destroying thousands of jobs.
工作本身并没有消失
Jobs are not being destroyed.
只不过被转移了地点
They're being relocated.
你认为这件事注定是错误的
The fact that you see that as inherently bad
说明你是个盲目的爱国者
means you're an irrational patriot.
或者说是极端爱国份子
To put it another way, a patriot.
爱国情节是与生俱来的
Patriotism is natural.
我们依赖于所属的群体  以保证个人安全
We've always relied on our tribes to keep us safe.
如果个人
It's helpful for society
对其所在的社会持正面观点
if its members have positive feelings
是有利于社会安定的
about that society.
反例就是伊朗的女人
Iranian women.
乌干达的变装同性恋
Drag queens in Uganda.
爱国主义说白了就是对不动产的忠诚
Patriotism is nothing but loyalty to real estate,
而这些土地
real estate that's been conquered 800 times
曾被不同文化背景的不同政权所统治
by 800 different regimes with 800 different cultures.
不论哪个时代的人  都认为祖国是最好的
But each time, it's just the best.
我以西班牙伊莎贝拉女王之名
I claim this burger in the name of
宣告这个汉堡归我了
Queen Isabella of Spain.
我去看看病人的情况
I'll go check on the patient.
我有丙肝
I have hepatitis C.
是我传给她的
She got it from me.
我爸爸怎么样了
Hey, how's my Dad doing?
很不错
Ah, great.
他的视觉恢复正常了
His vision's back to normal,
如果他整晚都没有复发
And if he remains asymptomatic through the night,
明天早上就可以出院了
we'll be able to release him in the morning.
能不能在九点前出院
Any chance that could happen before 9:00?
在他住院消息的冲击下
Our stock dropped a couple points today
股价跌了不少
with the news that he's sick.
我希望能在开市之前
I would love for him to get out of here
就让他出院
before the market opens.
请别见怪  但是...
No offense, but...
我觉得你父亲要关闭所有在美工厂
I think it's terrible your Dad's closing down
是很过分的决定
all your American operations.
我想他并不是出于图利而转移公司的
I don't think he's moving the company out of greed.
他是要离开这个伤心之地
He's moving it out of grief.
我的母亲  在四个月前去世了
My mom, she died four months ago.
死于非霍奇金淋巴瘤
Non-hodgkin's lymphoma, and...
住在满是回忆的家里  行驶在同样的路上
It's been hard for him-- living in their house,
物是人非  让他很伤感
driving down the same streets.
不断勾起他对我母亲的回忆
I mean, he's constantly reminded of her.
爸爸
Dad?
这里需要一个插管包
I need an intubation kit in here!
怎么回事
What's going on?
血管造影术显示  在肺左下叶
Angiography showed a hemorrhagic site
有一个出血点
in the left lower lobe.
我认为是高黏滞综合征
I think it could be hyperviscosity syndrome.
我们呆在福曼的办公室里
Are you sure Foreman's okay with this thing
他没关系吗
in his office?
他才不会发现呢
He's never gonna know.
事实上他不就在这里吗
He's actually in here right now.
血细胞计数和蛋白计数均正常
Blood count and protein count are normal.
我认为是高黏滞综合征
I think it could be hyperviscosity syndrome.
抱歉  不过在今天早上朴克向全院
Sorry, but after Park sent out here hospital-wide
发了那份不算道歉的道歉信后
non-apology apology this morning,
我认为抄袭是眼下最流行的
I assume that plagiarism is the new black.
如果那能让大家同情安德鲁斯...
If it makes Andrews look sympathetic...
学他只会让你更可悲
Copying him makes you look pathetic.
你要是不去上愤怒控制课  我给你钱
And I will pay you not to go to anger management classes.
会不会是凝血问题
What about another clotting problem?
凝血因子V缺乏症
Factor V Leiden deficiency.
有可能
It's possible.
亚当斯才是需要控制愤怒情绪的人
Adams is the one who needs to deal with her anger.
骨髓增生异常综合征
Myelodysplastic syndrome.
我听说了
I heard about your conversation
你跟病人女儿的对话
with the patient's daughter.
你的态度很恶劣
You were hostile.
那是因为他们公司的决定
Well, their company's making a decision
我强烈反对
I strongly disagree with.
但你对监狱里的种族主义者
Yet you were never anything but courteous
和强奸犯的态度可好得不得了
to the racists and rapists in prison.
难道你认可那些家伙的作为吗
Those guys made decisions you supported?
骨髓增生异常综合征
Myelodysplastic syndrome.
我猜跟你昨天早上参加的葬礼
I'm guessing it has something to do with the funeral
大有关系
you attended yesterday morning.
我是去参加面试了
I was at a job interview.
你九点一刻就来了
You got to work at 9:15.
离这里最近的一家就你的专科有招聘的医院
Closest hospital with an opening in your specialty
也有45分钟的路程
is 45 minutes away.
你在说谎
It's not possible.
节哀顺变
My condolences.
我不是去参加葬礼
I wasn't at a funeral.
那只剩下...
That just leaves...
不是面试
everywhere but a job interview.
出去
Get out.
是哪个小鬼
Who goes there?
快快现形
Reveal yourself!
赶快
Now.
我们会走的
Well, we would.
但整形外科还占着
But orthopedics is still squatting
我三分之二的办公室
in two thirds of my office,
真是怪了
which is weird,
要知道我昨晚给了张你巨额支票
'cause you got a large check last night.
由一家众所周知
From a corporation that's going through
周转不灵的公司开出
a very public belt-tightening,
就是说这是笔被迫捐款
means this donation was given under duress.
病患没有说明前因后果
Patient didn't tell me the whole story,
但他确实提到  若我们不兑现就太好了
but he did say he'd be thrilled if we didn't cash this.
五分钟后  这里有一个政策商议会
Got a policy review meeting in here in five minutes.
走好不送
Good-bye.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
摸你的屁股
Holding your ass.
这还用问吗
You really didn't know?
-豪斯...  -我只是想帮你
- House... - Just trying to help you out here.
我以为他肯定会一拳挥在我脸上
I figure for sure he'd punch me in the face,
就能证明那是正常反应了
thus proving it's a natural response.
老天  你自制力也太好了点吧
My god, you have super-human discipline.
臀肌也很紧致
And glutes.
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off me.
对不起
Sorry.
走吧
Go.
你那是想要干什么
Why...did you do that?
当然是为了我们的赌约
We have a bet.
他可是纪律委员会的主席
But he's the chair of the disciplinary committee.
别心心念念你的赌约了
Forget about the bet.
你俩还真得好好做做功课
You two really need to do your homework on me.
给病人注射活化蛋白C
Treat the patient with activated protein C.
如果他真有骨髓增生异常综合征的话
If he has myelodysplastic syndrome,
就会出血而死
he'll bleed out.
要是他是凝血因子V缺乏
And if he has Factor V Leiden deficiency,
那他就可能再出现血栓了
he'll throw another clot.
一点没错
Exactly.
这样就能确诊了
It's a conclusive test.
实际上半点风险都没有
There's no actual risk.
前提是你俩得时刻密切关注
As long as you're both paying attention,
医术也能胜任我的要求
and are both good enough to work here.
听说你们中有人觉得我是个大混蛋
I hear one of you thinks I'm a real bastard.
那应该是我
I guess that would be me.
你老板对我敲诈勒索
Your boss uses blackmail,
而你质疑我的职业道德
and you question my professional ethics?
你会为你新工厂的员工
Will you be instituting worker safety regulations
制定安全规章吗
in your new factories?
那是当然
Oh, absolutely.
那你也会为那些你即将雇佣的孩子们
What about juice boxes in the break room
在休息室准备果汁吗
for the children you'll be hiring?
对于美国公司滥用童工的那些指控
Charges of child exploitation against American companies
永远都是夸大其词
have been blown way out of proportion.
我有个侄子住在宿雾附近  今年十岁
My ten-year-old cousin lives near Cebu City.
他就在一家美国工厂里打工
Works at an American factory.
真为他难过
I am so sorry.
对他来说  这再好不过了
It's the best thing for him.
美国工厂虽然很糟
It sucks,
但是菲律宾的工厂更可怕
but the Filipino factories suck worse,
基本没有学校  有的话也烂得不得了
and the schools would suck if they existed.
对他全家来说  这已经是康庄大道了
So this is the family's best hope.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我这么痒正常吗
Is this supposed to itch like this?
痒
Itching.
有意思
Interesting.
没意思  症状已经消失了
Not interesting. Already went away.
更有意思了
Doubly interesting.
这下我们欠两个合理解释了
Means we have to explain
为何出现  又为何消失
the arrival and the departure.
你还真成熟  豪斯
That's real mature, House.
你这话什么意思
What do you mean?
我这明明就是出奇的幼稚
This is outlandishly childish.
这个宝贝可是我特别定制的
I custom-built this puppy.
装有106个LED灯泡
It's got 106 LEDs,
每一个的波长都略有不同
each one sending light to your eyes,
直直地射进你的眼睛里
slightly different wavelength.
把那玩意关上
Turn that off.
不同波长的光会刺激你的自主神经系统
Different wavelengths are stimulating your autonomic nervous system.
让你觉得好像坐在一条摇摆不定的船上
That's what's making you feel like you're on a boat in choppy waters.
太酷了
Oh ho ho!  Cool.
你该不会是
You think I'm not--
觉得我不会把这事告诉福曼医生吧
You think I'm not gonna go to Foreman with this?
你当然会告诉他了
Oh, you will.
然后我当然会否认
And...I'll deny it,
然后他当然会相信你
and he'll believe you.
不过站在这里的两位倒是觉得
But then these two believe that
保护公民工作权利得从自己做起
the policy of protecting American jobs starts at home.
所以是肯定不会帮你作证的
So they'll never testify against me.
那你什么也没法证明
And you won't be able to prove anything.
看见没  要是我对着他的脸来上一拳
Now, if I punched him in the face,
他就有证据了
that he could prove.
我隐约还记得你说过
I remember you saying something about
对房产的忠诚是多么的愚蠢
how loyalty to real estate was stupid.
这关系到能否拿回被窃取的财产
This is about reclaiming stolen property!
对于房产的忠诚确实愚蠢
Loyalty to real estate is stupid,
因为忠诚本身就是蠢事一桩
because loyalty is stupid.
先抨击爱国主义  现在又是忠诚
First patriotism, now loyalty.
你不会也讨厌冰激凌吧
You hate ice cream too?
法国香草味  确实讨厌
French vanilla, yeah.
一厢情愿地给自己找个归属
To willfully identify yourself as something else
是一种病态的自我表现方式
is a perversion of self-expression.
我有个想法
I had a thought.
撇开
Other than the fact
忠诚是一切有意义关系的建立基础的事实
that loyalty is the basis of all meaningful relationships.
他女儿还提到过
The daughter said that
她母亲死于非霍奇金淋巴瘤
her mother died of Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma.
要是那是误诊呢
What if she was misdiagnosed?
巧克力味还不错
Dutch chocolate's not bad.
就是这个了
Gotta give 'em that.
淋巴瘤可能是由病毒引起的
Her Lymphoma could have been caused by a virus,
T细胞白血病病毒I型
HTLV-1,
可能通过性行为传染给他
which our patient contracted through having sex with his wife.
也就是说  忠诚让他患上了癌症
In other words, loyalty gave him cancer.
这主意我喜欢
I like it.
对他进行放疗
Start him on radiation.
这是昌恩兄弟
Chang and Eng Bunker.
历史上最有名的连体双胞胎
It's the most famous conjoined twins in history.
2011年是他们诞生两百周年
2011 is the bicentennial of their birth.
最好的万圣节服装
The best halloween costumes
永远都让人看不懂
are always the ones that need an explanation.
怎么才来
What took you so long?
我已经痛失其中之一了
I already lost one of them.
撕裂伤的治疗要我帮忙吗
You need help with the lacerations?
不是  我会用保守疗法
No, I think I got palliative.
你怎么也不做些预防措施
Why don't you take preventative?
预防什么  他弄成这样是因为打架
Prevent what? He got in a fight.
还是他先动的手
Which he started.
也就是说他又暴躁又愚蠢
Which means he's both irascible and stupid.
我都告诉那个种族歧视兄弟会的醉鬼
I told the drunk, racist frat guy
这应该叫做连体双胞胎了
the proper term is "Conjoined twin,"
不是什么暹罗双胞胎
not "Siamese."
对于醉鬼还是兄弟会  我不予置评
I can't comment on the drunk or the frat.
但昌恩兄弟呢  确实出生于暹罗
But Change and Eng were both, in fact, born in Siam.
而且他们确实  是双胞胎
And they were, in fact, twins.
就像  如果你叫是理查德
If your name was Richard,
那我也可以叫你迪克
it would be okay for me to call you a Dick.
展示下你在愤怒控制课上学的废话吧
But maybe some of the tripe you learn in anger management class
也许他就不会二进宫了
might help keep this guy out of here the next time.
有时候  给那些罪有应得的人来一拳
Sometimes, it's incredibly satisfying
会让你感觉到格外的满足
to wind up and punch someone who really deserves it.
但如果你能想想后果的话
But when you think about the consequences--
这样就行了  走吧
Okay, let's go.
你不是让我帮他控制情绪吗
I thought you wanted me to help him with his anger.
不用了  我要的东西已经到手了
No, I got everything I need.
-有时候  -有时候
- Sometimes... - Sometimes...
给那些罪有应得的人来一拳
It's incredibly satisfying to wind up
会让你感觉到格外的满足
and punch someone who deserves it.
不知道委员会的人听后会怎么想
Wonder what the committee's gonna make of that.
这纯粹就是浪费时间
This is a waste of time.
罗宾不可能传染给我性病
There's no way that Robin gave me an STD.
我知道这很难接受
I know this is hard,
关于你妻子的事  我很抱歉
and I'm sorry about your wife.
如果你想找人谈谈的话
If you'd like to talk to someone,
我们医院有悲伤咨询师
we do have grief counselors at the hospital.
你说起话来跟我女儿一样
You sound like my daughter.
我很想我的妻子
I miss my wife,
但这并不影响我的经营决策
but it's not driving my decision-making.
你从88年开始就任首席执行官
You were CEO since 1988.
在你妻子过世后决定搬迁公司
You decided to move your company right after your wife died.
合理的解释就是你受了情感的影响
It stands to reason that your emotions factored in.
我妻子
My wife...
是我逗留此地的唯一原因
is the only thing that keeps me here.
我每周都去给她扫墓
I visit her grave once a week.
这么说  你女儿错了
So your daughter was wrong.
你就是需要
You just...really need
一大笔钱
a lot of money.
你听说过株式会社金刚组吗
You ever hear of Kongo Gumi?
是家成立于公元578年的日本建筑公司
Construction company in Japan founded in the year 578.
是家族企业
Family-owned and operated.
五十代人都是以建造寺庙为生
Building buddhist temples for 50 generations.
五年前破产了
We--went bankrupt five years ago.
你能想象他们最后一任执行官是什么感受吗
You have any idea how that last CEO must have felt?
对不起  我忍不住要动一下
Sorry, I have to move.
你在心律加速
Your heart rate is speeding up.
感觉胸闷吗
Do you feel any tightness in your chest?
是的  我以为是放射的关系
Yes, I figured it was from the radiation.
我想你犯心脏病了
I think you're having a heart attack.
请进
Come in.
威尔森医生
Dr. Wilson...
我有事请教
I need your advice.
我和豪斯拿一百块
I bet House $100
赌我不会在纪律听证会
that I wouldn't get fired
之后被解雇
after my disciplinary hearing.
自此以后  他仿佛
Ever since then, he's been acting like
当真想要让我被解雇
he's actually trying to get me fired.
那是因为他的确想让你被解雇
That's because he is actually trying to get you fired.
他讨厌我吗
Does he hate me?
估计和那没有关系
Not sure that's relevant to the equation.
那么就是为了一百块
So it's really over $100?
估计和钱没关系
Not sure the amount is relevant.
他捍卫的是他的尊严
He's fighting for his honor.
他会毁了我的前程
He'll ruin my career.
-估计也...  -如果我拿两百块
- Not sure that'...  - What if I bet him $200
赌我会被解雇呢
I will get fired.
他认为和同一个人下相互对立的赌注
He sees competing debts with the same person
是非常可耻的行为
as a disgrace to the game.
他可能会愈发地想要整垮你
He'll be even more motivated to beat you.
换作是你  你会怎么做呢
If you were me, what would you do?
你得给他些
You have to give him something
他视为比尊严还重要的东西
he values more than honor.
同时  你可以开始重新写简历了
And you should update your resume.
心电图和肌钙蛋白检测结果不明确
EKG and troponins were equivocal.
甚至无法确定病人
It's not even clear if our patient
是否犯了心脏病
just had a heart attack or what it was.
看看他是否有节段性室壁运动异常
Let's look at segmental wall motion abnormalities.
给他做个超声波检测
Get him an echo to confirm.
我需要二十万
I need $200,000.
自他入院后他的公司
His company's lost one third of its value
损失了三分之一的市值
since he was admitted.
所以你想进行内幕交易吗
And you want to do some insider trading?
这是经济犯罪
I take it felonies
有违你的假释条例吧
aren't a violation of your parole?
这不是内幕交易
It's not insider trading.
就是赌我能治好他的病
Just betting on myself to solve the case.
一旦治好了  他公司股价就会涨
Once we cure him, share price goes up,
我就还你钱
I pay you back.
不行
No.
不  你不能说"不"
No, you don't say "No."
你应该和我还价
You...make a counter offer.
我不会借钱给我的老板的
I'm not loaning my boss money.
好吧  我替你还价
Fine. I'll make you a counter.
十万块
$100,000.
二万块吧
$20,000.
我不买股票了  我买期权
I'll buy options instead of shares.
风险更大  不过收益也更多
More risk, but more upside.
最低就这个数了
But that's as low as I'm gonna go.
我能借你五千块
I could do $5,000.
真的  不准反悔
Really? No backsies.
如果  你的门诊时间翻倍的话
If...you double your clinic hours.
每周六小时
Six a week.
我见识过你对病人的不尊重
I've seen how you disrespect those patients.
所以你想要双倍数量的病人不被我尊重
So you want twice as many of them disrespected?
多花些时间在病人身上
Spend more hours with them,
你会对他们更人性些的
you'll treat them more humanely.
现在  去俄罗斯打场地面战
And this time, a land war in Russia
真是个好主意啊
will be a good idea.
成交吗
Deal?
以下是我的愚见
Here's what I'm thinking.
你出席了一次假释听证会
You went to a parole hearing,
他们拒绝了你以前病人的假释申请
where one of your old patients was denied.
这解释了你为什么穿礼服  为什么会迟到
Hence the attire, hence the tardiness,
尤其重要的是  为什么发这么大的火
most importantly hence the anger.
你认为在这里多做些好事
You think you can restore the cosmic balance
可以维持世间的平衡
by doing extra good here.
更让人不爽的是  这好事还要由我来做
More annoyingly, by having me doing it.
成交
And deal.
你知道  你这么做就是宣战了
Of course, you know... this means war.
是的  我知道
Oh, I know.
你会让战事升级
I mean, you'll escalate,
然后我会报复
And then I'll retaliate,
就这么礼尚往来地发展下去
And the cycle will continue
直到我们都做出过激行为
until we've both gone too far,
到那时  我可能因此停职
at which point, I'll maybe get suspended.
至于你  就回监狱去吧
And you'll go back to prison.
恶作剧万岁
Happy pranking.
超声波显示病人有室性心动过速
Patient had v-tach in the echo lab,
所以我们做了检查
so we capped him, but...
但冠状动脉没有堵塞
Coronary Arteries were clean.
这好比如果水管没问题的话
If the plumbing's fine,
就去检查下电路系统
check the electrical.
做个电生理检查
EP study.
好主意
Nice idea.
甚至还用了比喻
Even has a metaphor in it.
虽然比不上我的尊严
Not worth more than my honor.
但还是挺讨喜的
But delightful, all the same.
我不会输的
I'm not going to lose.
我大学室友现在是
My college roommate is the editor
《耶鲁法学观察》的编辑
of the Yale Law Review.
我的开场白正由她起草
She's writing my opening statement.
你会拥有一个华丽的失败
You will be eloquent in your loss.
归根结底就是你和他各执一词
This case boils down to he said, she said.
他说  "我在医院干了十五年了"
He said, "I've been working at this hospital for 15 years.
"而且我还参加了自我改善的课程"
"And I'm taking self-improvement classes."
她说  "我入院工作两个月"
She said, "I've been a fellow for two months,
"而且我性情古怪"
"and I'm kind of weird."
不对  他说的是  "我是个喝醉的白痴"
No, he said, "I'm a drunk idiot"
"以为能随便摸女生的屁股"
"who thinks he can grab girls' behinds
"而不会被追究责任"
"without ramifications."
等等  他当时醉了
Wait, he was drunk?
-还待在医院  -我告诉过福曼
- In the hospital? - I already told Foreman
他那晚喝过酒了
he'd been drinking that night.
安德鲁斯上的是性骚扰课程
Andrews was taking sexual harassment classes,
不是戒酒互助会
not AA.
意味着他没有因饮酒而受罚
That means he didn't get in trouble for drinking.
说明是福曼替他隐瞒了
Which means that Foreman signed off on it,
是他操办了这一切
which means that he set all the wheels in motion.
算了  我推断得太离谱了
Forget that. Wild speculation.
去做电生理检查吧
Go do the EP study.
你早就知道安德鲁斯那晚喝酒了
You already knew Andrews was drinking that night,
是吧
didn't you?
是的
Yes.
我认为你应该取消我的听证会
I think you should cancel my hearing.
我希望事态不会向我认为的方向发展
I hope this isn't going where I assume it's going.
是你把安德鲁斯牵涉进来的
You're the one who brought Andrews in.
这一切都是你操办的
You set the wheels in motion.
我们当时有个重危病人
We had a patient who was going to die
如果不做脑动静脉畸形栓塞治疗必死无疑
without an avm embolization.
安德鲁斯是我唯一能联系到的神经科医师
Andrews...was the only neurologist I could reach.
他告诉我他喝了几杯红酒
He told me had a few glasses of wine,
也知道他不该这么做
and that he shouldn't do it,
但他还说了  你很优秀
but he also said that you were good.
只要有人在旁指导  你已可以做栓塞治疗了
You were ready to do one, as long as you were supervised.
所以我们同意让他留下
So we agreed that he would come in,
但不能碰病人
but wouldn't touch the patient.
你的想法我可以理解
I can understand the rationalization.
那我们就看董事会怎么说
We'll see if the board agrees
我要在听证会上和盘托出
when I tell them the whole story at my hearing.
我已经说了
I already did.
上周我召开了一次内部听证会
I had a closed session hearing last week.
董事会决定扣除我两周的薪水
The board decided to dock me two weeks pay.
在豪斯手下做了两周
Been working for House for two weeks.
已经嫌长了
It's already too long.
右心房没有任何
No sign of any electrical abnormalities
心电图异常
in the right atrium.
我死定了
I'm so dead.
我觉得豪斯给我下了个套
I-I think House set me up.
你有没有
Have you sent
帮我写品行参考书给委员会
the committee a character reference for me?
我以为你不喜欢别人帮忙
I thought you don't like favors.
我不喜欢礼物  这不算礼物
I don't like gifts. It wouldn't be a gift.
你也只是说真话而已
I would just be you telling the truth.
我都不怎么了解你
I hardly know you.
血氧饱和度89
O2 sat is 89.
我们穿孔了吗  怎么会梗塞的
Did we perforate? Is he tamponading?
心率90  颈静脉平坦
Heart rate's only 90. Neck veins are flat.
那血氧饱和度怎么会低
Then why isn't he saturated?
他看着挺健康的
Seems healthy to me.
放他出院吧
Let's release him.
我手头以34美元卖出巴顿食品股票的期权
My option to sell Barton Foods at $34
要到期了
is about to expire.
人们以为他已经好转了
So they thought the patient would be better by now.
不然  我得损失两万美元
Instead, I am going to lose $20,000.
两万
20?
你的五千加上从威尔森那偷的五千
Your five plus the five I stole from wilson.
还有一万保证金额度
Plus the ten I got on margin.
你得找我的破产律师要钱去了
You're gonna have to talk to my bankruptcy attorney.
除非
Unless...
要拿回你的钱  确实有个方法
There is a way that you can get your money back.
给我二十万
Give me the full $200,000.
这样下去
And extrapolating,
明天你大概就要欠一百万了
tomorrow you'll owe just shy of $1 million.
是你自己惹的祸
It's your own fault.
是你逼我选择了期权
You forced me to go with the options here.
因为你生气  害我赔了钱
Your damn anger issues are screwing with my finances.
这次我只买平常的股票  平稳安全
Regular stock this time, nice and safe.
我没有生气
I'm not angry.
不知道你是不是想要惹我生气
I don't know if you're trying to make me angry.
你拒绝赌你自己赢
You refuse to bet on yourself.
这说明你缺乏自信
That means low self-esteem.
所以如果我给你二十万
So if I give you $200,000,
我就会又漂亮又聪明了
I'll feel smart and pretty.
缺乏自信可能源于
Low self-esteem can be brought on
被某个亲戚戳了痛处
by exposure to one's relatives.
穿得正式  还生气
Nice clothes and anger...
很典型
Classic symptoms.
家庭聚会
Family gathering.
你那天迟到
You were late the other day
是因为你在和
'cause you were having breakfast
外婆或是表亲谁谁的一起吃早餐
with grammy Adams or cousin it.
她催你快找个人嫁了
And she was nagging you about finding a husband.
好吧  你开始有点招人烦了
All right, this is getting annoying.
我直接告诉你得了
I'll just tell you what I was--
别剧透
No spoilers.
剧透最讨厌了
They ruin everything.
肺科在那边
Pulmonology was that way.
他的肺部问题不是肺的问题
Our patient's lung problem is not a lung problem.
是脑部问题
It's a brain problem.
我们去神经科咨询咨询
We're consulting with neurology.
那是我前任上司
That's my old boss.
你根本不觉得这和神经有关
You don't actually think this is neurological.
我不知道这和什么有关
I don't know what it is.
也许我应该
Maybe I should just
就让病人去死  因为找某些人帮忙
accept the patient's death, if getting help
可能会比较尴尬
can lead to awkwardness.
安德鲁斯医生
Dr. Andrews.
见过我的同事们
My associates.
亚当斯医生和朴克医生
Doctors Adams and Park.
很高兴见到你  亚当斯医生
Ah. Nice to meet you, Dr. Adams.
你好  朴克医生
Hello, Dr. Park.
你们俩认识啊
You two know each other?
世界真小
It's a small world.
朴克医生  能不能请你
Dr. Park, maybe you'll like to update
向我们可敬的同事
our esteemed colleague
讲讲病人的情况
on the condition of our patient.
视物显小症  出血
Micropsia, bleeding,
心动过速和呼吸困难
tachycardia, and difficulty breathing.
屁股不错吧
Cute butt, huh?
我们可以走了吗
Can we go now?
你真的想背对他吗
You really wanna turn your back on this guy?
抱歉  继续
Sorry. Carry on.
听上去可能是
It sounds like there could be
脊髓受累
spinal cord involvement.
有没考虑过正常颅压脑积水
Have you considered normal pressure hydrocephalus?
好吧  正常颅压脑积水
Okay, normal pressure hydrocephalus
一次
going once.
正常压力脑积水  两次
Normal pressure hydrocephalus going twice...
和脊髓无关
It's not his spinal cord,
是他心脏和大脑的连接问题
It's the wiring between his heart and his brain.
自主神经功能障碍综合征
Autonomic dysregulation syndrome.
做直立倾斜试验
You do a tilt table test,
看他的心率作何反应
see how his heart rate responds.
就能证实了
That'll confirm.
如果是正常颅压脑积水
Well, if he has normal pressure hydrocephalus,
直立倾斜试验可能致使他昏迷
a tilt table test could put him in a coma.
那他最好得的是自主神经功能障碍综合症吧
Then it's a good thing he has A.D.S.
你真相信自己的诊断吗
Do you really believe in this diagnosis?
因为如果这只是个斗气比赛
Because if this is just a pissing contest,
那说明你有严重的生理结构缺陷
you are at a severe anatomical disadvantage.
是自主神经功能障碍综合症
It's autonomic dysregulation syndrome.
不  是正常颅压脑积水
No...it's normal pressure hydrocephalus.
做脊髓液检测
Do a spinal fluid test to confirm.
我们要做直立倾斜试验
We're doing the tilt table.
真有道理
That makes sense.
比起福曼你更想被豪斯解雇是吗
You'd rather have House fire you than Foreman?
这场赌局是个测试
This bet's got to be a test.
测试我是否有能力和他一起工作
See if I can handle working with him.
我必须证明我有自信
I need to prove I have the confidence
来违抗他
to disobey him.
对于你的诊断  你有没有任何
Do you have any medical justification
医学上的理由
for your diagnosis?
症状相符  而且安德鲁斯就是个草包
The symptoms fit, and Andrews is a hack.
你觉得呢
Do you think I'm right?
走吧
Let's go.
不  你得准备听证会
No...you need to go prepare for your hearing.
还有15分钟  巴顿先生
15 more minutes, Mr. Barton.
一个激光换肤器不见了
A skin resurfacing laser is missing.
为什么来问我
And why are you asking me about it?
因为你替豪斯做事
Because you work for House.
豪斯要激光换肤器干什么
What would House want with a skin resurfacing laser?
我怎么知道  你见过吗
I have no idea. Have you seen it?
我的脚感觉很热
My feet feel hot.
那完全正常
That's completely normal.
不  但豪斯一直提到
No, but House has been talking about
他有多想把在监狱时的纹身洗掉
how badly he wants to remove those prison tats.
那机器很贵
It's a very expensive machine,
我希望能找回来
and I'd like it back.
有什么消息麻烦告诉我
Please tell me if you hear anything.
有多贵
How expensive?
二十万
$200,000.
就是他拿的
He took it.
我不知道
I have no idea.
朴克的听证会要开始了
Park's hearing's about to start.
你在为他掩饰
You're covering for him.
我以前经常这样
I did the same thing many times.
我的建议  设好
My advice to you-- figure out what line
你能为他所逾越的底线
you aren't willing to cross for him.
因为他最终还是会让你跨越它
Because, eventually, he'll ask you to cross it.
你的脚怎样了
How are your feet?
巴顿先生
Mr. Barton?
能听到我说话吗  巴顿先生
Can you hear me, Mr. Barton?
不
Oh, no.
此次召集纪律委员会开庭
We have convened the disciplinary committee
是为了裁定朴克智医生
to decide the appropriate action that should be taken
于今年十月七日
against Dr. Chi Park as a result of her actions
所采取的行为是否适当
on October 7th of this year.
朴克医生  你是否打算进行开庭陈述
Dr. Park, do you have an opening statement.
福曼医生  各位委员会委员
Dr. Foreman, members of the committee,
感谢你们给我这次机会
thank you for giving me this opportunity
与你们进行交流  我...
to speak to you today, I...
好消息
Good news.
你们可以取消听证会了
You can cancel the hearing.
因为我要亲自开除她
'cause I'm firing her myself.
她不是你能开除的
She's not yours to fire.
你们最好以唯命不从的理由把她开除
You guys better fire her for insubordination,
因为她的捣乱  我的病人陷入了昏迷
'cause she went rogue, and my patient is now in a coma.
我才是做测试的人
I'm the one who did the test.
不  那是我的主意
No, it was my idea!
你搞什么  豪斯
Seriously, House?
至少我有自知之明
At least I'm smart enough
不会不懂装懂
to know what I don't know.
她反抗我到过火了
She went out of her way to defy me!
她应该  该死  就应该直接开除她
She needs--damn it, you should just fire her!
很抱歉
My apologies.
很抱歉  朴克医生
My apologies, Dr. Park.
豪斯医生的意见
Dr. House's comments
当然不会在此次听证会上
will, of course, have no bearing
被采纳
on this hearing.
请继续
Please continue.
我...
I, uh...
我不敢相信你真这么做了
I can't believe you did that.
彼此彼此
Right back at ya.
我们的病人正在死去  我们需要些想法
Our patient's dying. We need theories.
应该是正常颅压脑积水
It's gotta be normal pressure hydrocephalus.
安德鲁斯预测到了昏迷
Andrews predicted the coma.
没错  但再傻的医生也有蒙对的时候
Yeah, but even a broken doctor's right twice a day.
病人没有出汗  发抖或行为古怪
Patient wasn't wet, wobbly, or wacky.
昏迷只是碰运气猜中的
Coma had to be a lucky guess.
如果你认为他是错的
If you didn't think he was right,
为什么还让我们去采集脊髓液呢
then why did you want us to collect his spinal fluid?
我没有  我想让你们去做直立倾斜实验
I didn't. I wanted you to do a tilt table test.
你的沟通方式真是太绝了
You have a wonderful way of communicating.
我知道朴克想进行直立倾斜测验
I knew Park wanted to do a tilt table.
如果她听了我的  我就是浪费了一小时
She listens to me, I waste an hour.
如果她违反我的命令
If she defies me...
我不仅得到了测试结果还赚了一百块
Then I get the test I want and my 100 bucks.
爽死了
Up high.
你真是个混蛋
You're an ass.
你生气了
You're angry.
没错  现在我是生气了
Yes! Now I'm angry.
我们就去做正常颅压脑积水的测试吧
Let's run the test for normal pressure hydrocephalus.
不
No.
还有什么可以解释这些症状
What else would explain our symptoms
并且让病人在测试过程中陷入昏迷的呢
and make our patient go into a coma during that test?
肝性脑病可能吗
How 'bout hepatic encephalopathy?
不会  我们已经测过肝酶了
No, we already tested his liver enzymes.
指标正常
They're normal.
或是他的肝脏已经
Or his liver's so far gone
没办法产生酶了
it can't even produce enzymes.
这想法太离谱了
That's desperate.
与症状相符
Fits the symptoms.
安德鲁斯就是个草包
And Andrews is a hack.
进行穿刺活检确认
Go biopsy to confirm.
除非你也想开个听证会
Unless you want your own hearing.
那你得先雇我
You'd have to hire me first.
威廉斯护士请到社会服务科
Nurse Williams to social services.
你现在充分认识到
So you do realize
在工作场所打人
that it is unacceptable to hit someone
是不应该的了吗
in the workplace?
是的  完全不应该
Yes, completely unacceptable.
我当时没动脑子
I wasn't thinking.
我猜  我的意思是  理论上讲
I guess, I mean-- yes, technically,
我一直在思考
I was thinking.
我只是...一切发生得太快了
I just...it happened so fast,
我
I did--I--
我...
I...
当时就好像...
It's like...
就好像我不是我了
It's like it wasn't even me.
我绝不会做那种事的
I would never do something like that.
虽然我那么做了
Even though I did.
对不起  我现在有点语无伦次了
I'm sorry, I'm not making any sense right now.
我...
I, um...
我不知道  我...
I don't know, I...
我真的很喜欢当医生
Just really love being a doctor so much.
我连一百块钱都没有...
And I barely even have $100 and...
请不要开除我
please don't fire me.
这理论比其它的可能性更大吗
Is this theory more promising than the others?
几小时内我们就能知道了
We'll know in a few hours.
你还撑得住吗
How are you holding up?
除了我爸还在昏迷以外...
Other than the fact that my dad's in a coma...
糟透了
terrible.
明天早上  我应该签署
Tomorrow morning, I am supposed to sign
一份文件  那会...
a piece of paper that will...
将公司转移
move the company
并断送数千员工的工作
and cost thousands of employees their jobs.
我以为你会希望看到公司
I thought you'd rather see the company
搬去新泽西而不是中国
go under in New Jersey than thrive in China.
那是我爸的愿望
It's what my dad wants.
公司还是他的
And it's still his company.
我只是在让公司保持运转
I'm really just keeping the seat warm.
如果他不能在明早前醒来
But unless he wakes up before tomorrow,
那份文件上就会是我的签名了
it's gonna be my signature on that piece of paper.
你不必签字的
You don't have to sign it.
一有结果我第一时间通知你
I'll let you know when we have the results.
活检结果正常  不是肝脏问题
Biopsy was clean. It's not his liver.
我还做了脊髓液检测
I also ran the spinal fluid test,
你是对的  安德鲁斯确实错了
and you were right that Andrews was wrong.
他的颅内压不正常  指标偏高
His ICP was not normal. It was elevated.
会不会是人体T细胞白血病病毒
What about HTLV?
早在三天前就被排除了
We ruled that out three days ago.
因为他的心脏问题  但是
Because of his heart problems, but--
一旦某些理论被否定了
Once something gets taken off the board,
我是唯一能将它们重新列入考虑范围的人
I'm the only one who's allowed to put it back on.
你欠我106804韩元
You owe me 106,804 won.
或者是100美元
or $100 U.S.
上帝啊  你真小心眼
God, but you're petty.
两个选项
Okay, so...two options.
要么查出这家伙的病因
Either we figure out what's wrong with this guy,
要么设法让他的公司在新泽西州
or we figure out how to make this company profitable
也能营利
in New Jersey.
东部马脑炎
Eastern Equine Encephalitis?
我们在思考问题
Thinking in here!
脑部扫描显示
Brain scans indicate
有可能是罗阿罗阿丝虫病
it could be Loa Loa Disease.
给我关掉
Ah, shut it off!
显然现在打人也没事了
Apparently we're allowed to do this now.
豪斯  出去
Get out of here, House!
给病人做血浆置换
Start the patient on plasmapheresis.
一小时后他就会醒过来
He'll wake up in an hour.
有你做邻居真开心
It's been a pleasure having you in the neighborhood.
本诊断的灵感来自字母Y
This diagnosis was brought to you by the letter "Y."
爸
Dad...
上帝  你没事了
God, you're okay.
我口渴
I'm thirsty.
活着就是比死了麻烦
That's a side effect of not dying.
发现是你的血液粘稠  血糖高
Turns out your blood was getting thick and syrupy.
Y字型抗体聚集成团
Complexes of large, Y-shaped antibodies
阻塞了血管
were clogging up your blood vessels,
引起你全身器官接连衰竭
causing your organs to shut down one by one.
通常来说  高粘滞血症的成因是
Now, usually with Hyperviscosity Syndrome,
红细胞计数升高
it's caused by an elevated blood count
或者血蛋白升高
or protein count.
由于你患有风湿性关节炎
Yours eluded us
因而升高的是抗体
'cause it was caused by antibodies
误导了我们
from your rheumatoid arthritis.
现在我们把抗体滤除
Now that they're being filtered out,
你的血液就
the blood would be...
甜面酱变酱油了
a little less duck sauce and a little more soy sauce.
这么说我会痊愈
So I'm gonna be completely cured.
这可不是你一个人的事情
It's not all about you.
你公司的股价
Your stock price
也会恢复如初
will be completely cured,
只要你签了这个
once you sign this.
这是一份新闻声明
It's a press release.
声明你身体健康  即将恢复工作
It says that you're healthy, you're going back to work,
并且准备签署
and you're signing the lease
将公司移往中国的正式合同
that officially moves the company to China.
他才刚醒过来
He just woke up.
爸  这事不急
Dad, you don't have to deal with this right now.
事实上
Ah, mm, yeah, actually...
一定要现在
He does.
因为股市九点就开盘了
'cause the market opens at 9:00 a.m.
这对我很重要
And this means a lot to me.
你还记得我吧
You may remember me
是我救你一命的
from the time I saved your life.
你执意搬迁工厂  就没有我了
If you move it, it'll be without me.
我知道你一直都反对
I know you object.
我知道你不同意...
I know you disagree with...
爸
Dad...
我不能这么做
I can't do it.
如果真是为了这个家
If this is really about family,
你就不要这样做
You will not do this.
早上好
Morning.
这次咱走运
Got lucky this time.
不是你走运
No, you didn't.
我跟你赌是为了让你
I made this bet so you'd stop
不要极力炒掉朴克
actively trying to fire Park
至少保持中立
so you'd be neutral.
而你破例费心帮她
You went out of your way to help her.
她明显已经赢得了你的尊重
She obviously earned your respect,
通过了你的什么测试...
passed whatever test you...
我去了她的听证会上捣乱
I sabotaged her hearing.
校报你还看的吧
You do read the school paper, don't you?
如果你真是去破坏她听证会的
If you had sabotaged her hearing,
她就不会仅仅被小施惩戒了
she would have gotten more than a slap on the wrist.
你行动的实际效果是让她情绪激动
What you actually did was make her emotional
让董事会成员视她为受害者
and make the board members see her as a victim.
因为董事会不喜欢
'cause the panel feels badly
险些害死病人的无能医生
for incompetent doctors who nearly kill people.
你知道董事会的人都恨你
You know that everyone on that panel hates you.
你提出要解雇某人
You know the minute you recommend firing anyone,
他们立刻开始研究要给那人多少奖金
they start discussing how big a bonus to give them.
这话真伤人
That's just hurtful.
事实上  从你手里赢一百美元
The fact is, winning $100 from you
给我带来的欢乐
gives me more pleasure
远胜过从她那里赢一百美元
than winning $100 from her.
这是你的五千
Here's your five grand.
什么五千
What five grand?
只管拿着  相信我
Just take it. Trust me.
发现她在公园里睡觉
Found her sleeping in the park.
她说老爸不爱她  她就离家出走了
Said she ran away because her daddy didn't love her.
事情就是这个样子
And that is exactly what happened...
至少你不能证实不是
As far as you can prove.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你今天不用进监狱
You're not going to jail...today.
可是你也清楚
But you do know
我不能允许你愈演愈烈
I just can't let this slide.
领导得有威严
You need to keep up your rep.
好吧  门诊时间
Fine. Clinic hours.
双倍
I'll double them.
很好  每周十二小时
Okay. 12 hours a week.
不
No...
三乘二等于六
Three times two equals six.
三乘二再乘二等于十二
And 3 times 2 times 2 is 12.
我知道你跟亚当斯的约定
I know about your deal with Adams.
给奇斯和陶博打电话
Call Chase and Taub.
叫他们回来上班
Get 'em in here.
男孩们回来了[有同名电影]
The boys are back.
这张支票的数额比起我告诉你
This check is for significantly more
筹建诊断科所需
than what I told you it would take
多出很多
to fund the department.
我知道
I know.
你呼我
You paged me?
恭喜
Congratulations.
那天早上你发现男朋友出轨
You caught your boyfriend cheating that morning.
大吵一架
You had a big fight.
所以才迟到
That's why you were late.
对病人重检性病
You re-pitched an S.T.D.
说话张口闭口
You haven't gotten two consecutive minutes
不离"忠诚"二字
without using the word "Loyalty,"
反映了你的愤怒  不自信
which explains the anger and the low self-esteem,
你刻意装扮是因为
and the desire to feel pretty...
被抛弃后渴望感到自己漂亮
after having been rejected explains the clothes.
不是我男朋友
It wasn't my boyfriend.
是我丈夫
It was my husband.
我那天去了律师事务所签离婚协议
I was at my lawyer's office signing the divorce papers.
我错过了你已婚这个事实
I missed the fact that you were married.
我们分居已经快一年了
We've been separated for almost a year.
已是过往烟云
So...old news?
不再愤怒了吗
No anger left?
付过钱了  随便砸
It's all bought and paid for.